[
    {
        "question": "Which city was Lionel Messi born and raised?",
        "choice1": "Buenos Aires",
        "choice2": "Rosario",
        "choice3": "Mendoza",
        "choice4": "Cordoba",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team did Messi play for as a youngster?",
        "choice1": "Estudiantes",
        "choice2": "River Plate",
        "choice3": "Newell's Old Boys",
        "choice4": "Rosario Central",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What happened on Lionel Messi’s Argentina debut vs Hungary?",
        "choice1": "He was sent off",
        "choice2": "He scored a hat-trick",
        "choice3": "He was stretchered off",
        "choice4": "An opponent slapped him",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which year did Lionel Messi win his first Ballon d’Or?",
        "choice1": "2007",
        "choice2": "2008",
        "choice3": "2009",
        "choice4": "2010",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What were Messi’s two Barcelona squad numbers before No. 10?",
        "choice1": "29 & 17",
        "choice2": "30 & 11",
        "choice3": "37 & 19",
        "choice4": "30 & 19",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Messi’s eldest son?",
        "choice1": "Matteo",
        "choice2": "Thiago",
        "choice3": "Ciro",
        "choice4": "Sergio",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Messi’s wife?",
        "choice1": "Christina",
        "choice2": "Maria",
        "choice3": "Lucia",
        "choice4": "Antonella",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which other country could Messi have played international football for?",
        "choice1": "Uruguay",
        "choice2": "Spain",
        "choice3": "Brazil",
        "choice4": "Colombia",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Messi scored five goals in one game against which of these clubs?",
        "choice1": "Bayer Leverkusen",
        "choice2": "Arsenal",
        "choice3": "Sevilla",
        "choice4": "Valencia",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is unusual about Messi’s house in Barcelona?",
        "choice1": "Most Expensive House in Spain",
        "choice2": "Planes can’t fly over it",
        "choice3": "It has an underground nigntclub",
        "choice4": "It has 30 bedrooms",
        "answer": 2
    }
]